{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "Ann's room is _____ than Dan's .",
      "correctAnswer": "cleaner",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kim's dress is _____ than Emma's . ",
      "correctAnswer": "dirtier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more dirty"
    },
    {
      "question": "A cake is _____ than an orange .",
      "correctAnswer": "sweeter",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more sweet"
    },
    {
      "question": "A cat is _____ than a crocodile .",
      "correctAnswer": "nicer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more nice"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jill is _____ than Max .",
      "correctAnswer": "more active",
      "incorrectAnswers": "activer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sam is _____ than Ken .",
      "correctAnswer": "braver",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more brave"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is _____ than her father .",
      "correctAnswer": "calmer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more calm"
    },
    {
      "question": "My book is _____ than his book .",
      "correctAnswer": "more interesting",
      "incorrectAnswers": "interestinger"
    },
    {
      "question": "Juice is _____ than water .",
      "correctAnswer": "tastier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more tasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "My car is _____ than your car .",
      "correctAnswer": "slower",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more slow"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is _____ than his brother .",
      "correctAnswer": "greedier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more greedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tim is _____ than Tom .",
      "correctAnswer": "taller",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more tall"
    },
    {
      "question": "My room is _____ than my parents' room .",
      "correctAnswer": "smaller",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more small"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mary is _____ than Dina .",
      "correctAnswer": "plumper",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more plump"
    },
    {
      "question": "My brother is _____ than her brother .",
      "correctAnswer": "more handsome",
      "incorrectAnswers": "handsomer"
    },
    {
      "question": "This book is _____ than that one . ",
      "correctAnswer": "thinner",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more thin"
    },
    {
      "question": "Our teacher is the _____ teacher in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "kindest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most kind"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is the _____ girl in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "prettiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most pretty"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is the _____ boy in our school !",
      "correctAnswer": "rudest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most rude"
    },
    {
      "question": "My mum is the _____ woman in our family .",
      "correctAnswer": "most serious",
      "incorrectAnswers": "seriousnest"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have many books and this is the _____ one .",
      "correctAnswer": "thickest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most thick"
    },
    {
      "question": "July is the _____ month .",
      "correctAnswer": "hottest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "January is the _____ month .",
      "correctAnswer": "coldest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "Our house is the _____ one on our street .",
      "correctAnswer": "biggest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most big"
    },
    {
      "question": "My room is the _____ one in our flat .",
      "correctAnswer": "smallest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most small"
    },
    {
      "question": "My sister is the _____ girl in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "most beautiful",
      "incorrectAnswers": "beautifulest"
    },
    {
      "question": "She has the _____ hair in our family .",
      "correctAnswer": "longest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most long"
    },
    {
      "question": "This exercise is the _____ one .",
      "correctAnswer": "easiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is the _____ girl in the class .",
      "correctAnswer": "cleverest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most clever"
    },



    {
      "question": "Ann is _____ than her brother .",
      "correctAnswer": "younger",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more young"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jane's hair is _____ than Kate's hair .",
      "correctAnswer": "curlier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more curly"
    },
    {
      "question": "Victor is _____ than Sam .",
      "correctAnswer": "more creative",
      "incorrectAnswers": "creativer"
    },
    {
      "question": "For me, Physics is _____ than Literature .",
      "correctAnswer": "more boring",
      "incorrectAnswers": "boringer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dan is _____ than Emma .",
      "correctAnswer": "more hard-working",
      "incorrectAnswers": "harder-working"
    },
    {
      "question": "Max is _____ than Bill .",
      "correctAnswer": "lazier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more lazy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nancy is _____ than Robin .",
      "correctAnswer": "cleverer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more clever"
    },
    {
      "question": "This sofa is _____ than that armchair .",
      "correctAnswer": "more comfortable",
      "incorrectAnswers": "comfortabler"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mike's flat is _____ than Will's flat .",
      "correctAnswer": "more modern",
      "incorrectAnswers": "moderner"
    },
    {
      "question": "The weather today is _____ than yesterday .",
      "correctAnswer": "gloomier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more gloomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Steve's room is _____ than Dustine's room .",
      "correctAnswer": "more stylish",
      "incorrectAnswers": "stylisher"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will is _____ than Lucas .",
      "correctAnswer": "more polite",
      "incorrectAnswers": "politer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will is the _____ boy in our company .",
      "correctAnswer": "youngest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more young"
    },
    {
      "question": "Steve is the _____ boy in his class .",
      "correctAnswer": "oldest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more old"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dustine is the _____ person in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "most creative",
      "incorrectAnswers": "creativest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Physics is the _____ school subject .",
      "correctAnswer": "most boring",
      "incorrectAnswers": "boringest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jonathan is the _____ boy in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "most hard-working",
      "incorrectAnswers": "hardest-working"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lucas is the _____ person I know .",
      "correctAnswer": "laziest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most lazy"
    },
    {
      "question": "This bed is the _____ one .",
      "correctAnswer": "most uncomfortable",
      "incorrectAnswers": "uncomfortablest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nancy's room is the _____ one in our house .",
      "correctAnswer": "most stylish",
      "incorrectAnswers": "stylishest"
    },
    {
      "question": "His father is the _____ person in our family .",
      "correctAnswer": "most modern",
      "incorrectAnswers": "modernest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Today is the _____ day of this week .",
      "correctAnswer": "brightest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most bright"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is the _____ person in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "gloomiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most gloomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "This sofa is the _____ one .",
      "correctAnswer": "most comfortable",
      "incorrectAnswers": "comfortablest"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "Your room is _____ # than my room .",
      "correctAnswer": "cleaner",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most cleaner"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kim's socks are _____ # than Sam's socks .",
      "correctAnswer": "dirtier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "dirtiest"
    },
    {
      "question": "A pie is _____ # than an apple .",
      "correctAnswer": "sweeter",
      "incorrectAnswers": "sweetest"
    },
    {
      "question": "A rabbit is _____ # than a frog .",
      "correctAnswer": "nicer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "nicest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sam is the _____ # boy in my class .",
      "correctAnswer": "most active",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more active"
    },
    {
      "question": "My dog is the _____ # animal in the world !",
      "correctAnswer": "bravest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most brave"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is _____ # than her brother .",
      "correctAnswer": "calmer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "calmest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Victor is _____ # than Emma .",
      "correctAnswer": "friendlier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more friendly"
    },
    {
      "question": "This book is _____ # than that one .",
      "correctAnswer": "more interesting",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most interesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "A banana is _____ # than a lemon .",
      "correctAnswer": "tastier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "tastiest"
    },
    {
      "question": "A car is _____ # than a plane .",
      "correctAnswer": "slower",
      "incorrectAnswers": "slowest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Max is the _____ # boy in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "tallest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "taller"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pam is the _____ # boy in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "greediest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "greedier"
    },
    {
      "question": "A mouse is _____ # than an elephant .",
      "correctAnswer": "smaller",
      "incorrectAnswers": "smallest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Betty is _____ # than Veronica .",
      "correctAnswer": "plumper",
      "incorrectAnswers": "plumpest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ken is the _____ # boy in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "most handsome",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more handsome"
    },
    {
      "question": "My book is _____ # than her book .",
      "correctAnswer": "thinner",
      "incorrectAnswers": "thinnest"
    },
    {
      "question": "My teacher is the _____ # teacher in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "kindest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "kinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ella is the _____ # girl in my class .",
      "correctAnswer": "prettiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "prettier"
    },
    {
      "question": "Luc is _____ # than Alex .",
      "correctAnswer": "ruder",
      "incorrectAnswers": "rudest"
    },
    {
      "question": "My grandfather is the _____ # man in our family .",
      "correctAnswer": "most serious",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more serious"
    },
    {
      "question": "Today is the _____ # day of the year .",
      "correctAnswer": "hottest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "hotter"
    },
    {
      "question": "His book is _____ # than my book .",
      "correctAnswer": "thicker",
      "incorrectAnswers": "thickest"
    },
    {
      "question": "September is not the _____ # month of the year .",
      "correctAnswer": "coldest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "colder"
    },
    {
      "question": "Her backpack is _____ # than my backpack .",
      "correctAnswer": "bigger",
      "incorrectAnswers": "biggest"
    },
    {
      "question": "My mum is the _____ # woman in the world !",
      "correctAnswer": "most beautiful",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "Her hair is _____ # than Pam's hair .",
      "correctAnswer": "longer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "longest"
    },
    {
      "question": "This task is the _____ # one .",
      "correctAnswer": "easiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "easier"
    },




    {
      "question": "Ann is ___ # than her brother .",
      "correctAnswer": "younger",
      "incorrectAnswers": "youngest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jane's hair is _____ # than Kate's hair .",
      "correctAnswer": "curlier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "curliest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Victor is _____ # than Sam .",
      "correctAnswer": "more creative",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most creative"
    },
    {
      "question": "For me, Physics is _____ # than Literature .",
      "correctAnswer": "more boring",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most boring"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dan is _____ # than Emma .",
      "correctAnswer": "more hard-working",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most hard-working"
    },
    {
      "question": "Max is _____ # than Bill .",
      "correctAnswer": "lazier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "laziest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nancy is _____ # than Robin .",
      "correctAnswer": "cleverer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "cleverest"
    },
    {
      "question": "This sofa is _____ # than that armchair .",
      "correctAnswer": "more comfortable",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most comfortable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mike's flat is _____ # than Will's flat .",
      "correctAnswer": "more modern",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most modern"
    },
    {
      "question": "The weather today is _____ # than yesterday .",
      "correctAnswer": "gloomier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "gloomiest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Steve's room is _____ # than Dustine's room .",
      "correctAnswer": "more stylish",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most stylish"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will is _____ # than Lucas .",
      "correctAnswer": "more polite",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most polite"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will is the _____ # boy in our company .",
      "correctAnswer": "youngest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "younger"
    },
    {
      "question": "Steve is the _____ # boy in his class .",
      "correctAnswer": "oldest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "older"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dustine is the _____ # person in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "most creative",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more creative"
    },
    {
      "question": "Physics is the _____ # school subject .",
      "correctAnswer": "most boring",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more boring"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jonathan is the _____ # boy in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "most hard-working",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more hard-working"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lucas is the _____ # person I know .",
      "correctAnswer": "laziest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "lazier"
    },
    {
      "question": "This bed is the _____ # one .",
      "correctAnswer": "most uncomfortable",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more uncomfortable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nancy's room is the _____ # one in our house .",
      "correctAnswer": "most stylish",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more stylish"
    },
    {
      "question": "His father is the _____ # person in our family .",
      "correctAnswer": "most modern",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more modern"
    },
    {
      "question": "Today is the _____ # day of this week .",
      "correctAnswer": "brightest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "brighter"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is the _____ # person in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "gloomiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "gloomier"
    },
    {
      "question": "This sofa is the _____ # one .",
      "correctAnswer": "most comfortable",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more comfortable"
    }
  ]
}